[
  {
    id: 1,
    question: "1.Your luggage consists of",
    answer: "auditory",
    options: [
      "Accessories, iPhone, magazine",
      "A book, swimsuit, and sunglasses",
      "A pair of hiking boots, Jackets and backpack",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 2,
    question: "After a long day of work, you usually:",
    answer: "visual",
    options: [
      "Cook dinner and watch your favourite movie",
      "Study a new language or watch a documentary",
      "Get dressed for your sports game or workout",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "On vacation, you are most likely to read",
    answer: "audi",
    options: [
      "A novel",
      "A book to prepare me for the trip ahead",
      "Travel Journeys of a Lifetime",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question:
      "You wake up one morning, pack a bag, and fly anywhere in the world, where do you go?",
    answer: "audi",
    options: [
      "Maui to take a refreshing stroll along the seaside streets of Lahaina and the stunning beaches of Kaanapli",
      "Alaska to take a glacier tour, enjoy nature and find mysterious petroglyphs",
      "Petra which is an entire city carved out of a stone canyon, built by an ancient Arab civilization.",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question:
      "You’re on vacation and it’s late. You still haven’t eaten dinner so you:",
    answer: "Central Processing Unit",
    options: [
      "Head back to your room and order room service",
      "Ask a local to suggest an authentic ethnic restaurant",
      "Find the busiest restaurant and take a seat at the bar",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "On vacation, you would rather:",
    answer: "audi",
    options: [
      "Enjoy an afternoon at the spa in the Bahamas",
      "Explore the cobblestoned streets of old villages in Prague",
      "Whitewater raft in Costa Rica",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "To enjoy the outdoors, you:",
    answer: "audi",
    options: [
      " Socialize in Central Park",
      "Enjoy a coffee on a patio in Venice",
      "Go skiing / snowboarding to Whistler",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "You’re on vacation. Where do you stay?",
    answer: "Central Processing Unit",
    options: [
      "At an all-inclusive resort",
      "I find a boutique hotel or local bed and breakfast",
      "Nowhere specific. I go with the flow",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "What transportation would you rather have in your vacation?",
    answer: "audi",
    options: [
      "Anything arranged by the hotel",
      "Local driver",
      "When I get there, I will see what I find",
    ],
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "10.Where would you rather live?",
    answer: "Central Processing Unit",
    options: [
      "Nothing compares to my country",
      "Europe. The culture is my thing",
      "Anywhere exotic",
    ],
  },
];